Guide to the Greater Kansas City Council on Religion and Race Collection
University of Kansas
- RH MS R232
  - Oversize newspaper articles regarding racial and political issues, 1957-1977 (Folder Folder 1-3)